MORGAN DIEDERICH: Hey, all.
I just want to walk you
through your Canvas page
and talk a little bit
about important things you
need to know as we
dive into this course.
So I know a lot of you all like
to look at the what's coming up,
right.
So if we look from a
student perspective,
you're going to see all
of your assignments due.
This is great, but I would
actually really encourage
you to come to the home page
every time, because this
is going to be laid out in a
way that kind of helps walk you
through each module.
This module will
change every week.
And remember, our weeks
run from Saturday to Friday
with everything for
the week being due
on either Wednesday or Fridays.
And this is helpful because
it gives you the weekend
to work on it, but it
also gives you the space
through the week if you
have questions left over
from the weekend, if
you prefer to work on it
in the weekend to ask before.
If you are on a roll, maybe you
are understanding it awesome,
right?
You only have to do each
practice assignment once.
You crush the test your
knowledge assignments
and it shouldn't
take you too long.
I do have these tags of
how long I would expect
the average student to take.
So in this particular case,
this week's practice problems,
there's quite a few
because we really want
to jump in and get started.
I estimate the average
user is probably
going to take a little
under four hours
to get through the learning
material and practice
problems combined.
So the learning
resources is going
to be due on Wednesday
typically this week.
I am giving you a
little bit extra time.
And you'll have a video
that you can follow along
in Excel with me.
And then you also have
the textbook links
if you prefer, just
to link through here.
I do require that each week
you do submit something just
very light, just to
acknowledge that you
did go through the learning
material because that way,
you're starting to see
the why behind what
we're doing in Excel
and a lot of reasoning
that I go through as I'm
trying to answer a problem.
The practice questions are
really great at understanding
the kind of nuances of the
tool, but it's very prescriptive
and step by step,
which is great.
But I want you to get
both sides so that way
you can have that confidence
to learn new skills outside
of this class.
So each week, you're going
to have a learning resources
assignment typically
due on Wednesdays.
Your practice problems also
typically do on Wednesdays.
You have unlimited attempts
at these practice problems.
So it is very likely that
you could be getting 100
in this section of the
grade breakdown, which
is if you read the syllabus
is worth 40% of your grade.
Then each week by Fridays--
and again, if you're cruising,
you're working on Saturday
and you're feeling really great
about your practice problems
and you want to attempt
these, go for it.
You can do it on Saturday.
I'm not going to make
you do it on Fridays.
You're going to have
your test your knowledge.
Usually, it's going to
be between one or two.
Typically, one.
Again, this first
week is going to be
a little bit more intensive.
And you get two attempts on
these test your knowledge
assignments.
Sometimes, you might goof
something up a little bit
and you're like, oh shoot, I
actually knew how to do that.
Then, you're able to
go and correct it.
Or this is also a good signal
to say, oh, I didn't actually
understand what I was doing.
That's when you need to set
up a time to meet with me.
Same thing as if
you're taking maybe
to 45 minutes longer than the
anticipated time on the practice
problems.
That's what I need you to pause
and set time up to meet with me,
or start asking questions
in our weekly Q&A form,
because I want
you to understand.
And a little bit of
frustration is good.
A little bit of frustration
is how we learn.
But if it starts to get
unmanageable and feel like it's
dragging you down more
than helping you learn,
that's not what we want.
I want you to be a confident
learner, and so meet with me
and we can talk over where
something may not be clicking.
And we can start tailoring
examples and explanations
specifically to you.
That's why you're
paying USU this tuition.
And so please use
me as a resource.
On the home page, you can always
book a time to meet with me.
My calendar is
completely open to you
all, unless I have
another meeting scheduled.
And I do have evening
hours on Thursday
and early morning
hours on another day.
And my formal office hour for
this class is Friday at 12:00,
but I do anticipate that most
everybody will just book a time
that works for you.
You all are busy, you
have lots of classes.
A lot of you may be
working, have families.
So this is to help be as
flexible as you need to be.
Please review the
syllabus because this
will tell you
everything that you
need to know about the course.
We'll jump back in really quick.
Super important, this
tells you overall
what our IDEA
objectives are, how
are different assignments
mapped to that.
I'm not giving you assignments
just to fill empty space
or make you feel like
you're being busy.
These assignments
are specifically
designed to help your learning
and help your learning
in very specific
ways that we can
continue to track
on how I can further
improve as an instructor.
You do need to install Excel for
Desktop before you get started
and MyEducator.
So if you come back to the home
page and our models pop up,
I need you to click on
MyEducator Canvas Connect.
And what this does is this takes
you to our interactive textbook.
And our interactive
textbook allows
you to get that immediate
feedback on those practice
problems, as well as to
test your knowledge week's
weekly assignments, which is
super nice because then you're
able to be like, oh,
why didn't I get that?
And then it'll actually
link you to a video
within the textbook,
which is super nice.
So I really recommend
you watch my video first,
then skim the textbook, then
launch into your practice
problems, and then go back to
the textbook or my video as
needed.
OK, so go through
this introduction
though, because this is going
to help you get that MyEducator
Add-in, which you need to
do those practice problems.
And then it'll help you
understand how that looks.
It's very cool.
You essentially just copy
it and you go to your Excel.
And once you're in
your Excel for Desktop,
there's this add-in.
And then you just paste
that code it gives you,
and it's going to
populate data and give you
tasks to work on all
directly in the tool, which
is one of the things I
really like about this fender
is it lets you work
within the tool itself.
We're also going to have a few
critical thinking assignments,
and that is to mostly
just get you thinking
about who uses Excel, reflect
on your own learning approaches
and how that can be applied
as you leave this class
and move on to other
classes that use Excel
and eventually into
your own careers.
And learn from a few other
people, especially alumni,
and how they use Excel,
even if they don't
have analysts in their title.
And so go ahead this
week, make sure you're
reading the syllabus.
And then we're getting
started in Excel.
We're hitting the
ground running,
and I'm excited to
have you in class.